Huh? Who's that?
咦 誰啊 他是誰
Hey, boss. Wait for me.
喂 老大你等等我啊
Didn't you say I could do whatever I wanted?
你不是說隨我的便嗎
So I destroyed the roof and ran over here.
所以我就把屋頂弄壞然後跑過來了
You had already exceeded the agreed-upon time limit of 3 minutes.
那時妳已經超過我們約定的三分鐘了
Hmph.
唔
What's wrong?
怎麼了
I just had a strange feeling.
沒什麼 我只是感覺有點奇怪
Strange feeling?
什麼奇怪
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
《屍體如山的死亡遊戲》
(Episode 19: The Friends)
(#19 The Friends-親友-)
I'm sorry.
抱歉
I shouldn't have dragged you into what's basically my mess.
我不該把你們也捲進我的事情裡來
But, Mr. Iwa, it's no longer just your problem.
這已經不只是岩先生你的問題了吧
Your reaction to Prosecutor Hosorogi's issues was far too personal.
不過我覺得你確實在細呂木監察官 的事情上太過感情用事了
Um.
唔
Given Solitaire's involved,
只要跟雪天鴉有關
this has always been under the jurisdiction of Comps-3.
這本來就在我們三輯的職責範圍之內
You're right.
沒錯
Now that the media's gotten a whiff of the Habaki case,
不過媒體也察覺到幅木的事情了
this is gonna get big.
看來這件事要鬧大了
Leader, you could become the target of reporters yourself.
係長你也有可能會被人盯上
It might be best for you to keep a low profile for now.
你還是暫時不要在外面露面比較好
Yatsu, pops.
八津…大叔…
Sorry. We weren't able to locate Habaki.
抱歉 結果我們還是沒能找到幅木
Never mind.
算了 沒關係
I want to seize him before he escapes overseas,
雖然我希望能在他逃往國外前抓到他
but we don't know the scope or magnitude of his organization.
可我們不知道對方組織的規模和實力
Don't let your guard down.
千萬不能掉以輕心
Yes.
是啊
Let's just hope we can end this before it comes to that.
希望我們能在那之前跟他做個了斷
I don't remember summoning you here, Your Majesty.
我不記得我有叫您過來 陛下
Please, don't be so cold.
你別那麼冷漠嘛
Just coming out here was tough.
我為了過來 可是吃了不少苦頭呢
Moreover, you ignored my advice 100 years ago.
而且 一百年前你不聽我的勸阻
Perhaps it's your turn to suffer now.
這次該輪到你吃虧了吧
Relax.
放心吧
I came here without permission.
是我擅自過來的
So I'll be gone soon enough.
我很快就走
But how splendid that I was able to learn the words from this side, thanks to you.
不過多虧了你 我學會了這邊的語言 真是太好了
What a cutie.
好可愛
This world seems like a lot of fun.
這邊的世界挺有趣的嘛
Everyone wants to have a firsthand look.
大家都想親眼看一看
I apologize, but…
抱歉 但是…
It's okay.
沒事
I will wait patiently.
我會慢慢等你的
Until your heart wishes it so.
直到你的內心願意接受為止
Someday…
這一天
For certain…
總會到來的
Who is he?
他是…
A friend of mine.
他是我的朋友
From the other world.
他來自那邊的世界
I see.
是嗎
You have a good friend.
你有一個好朋友
That's right.
是啊 沒錯
Although I'm not sure when it comes to this world…
雖然我不知道 對於這個世界來說如何
But I know that you are still you,
但我知道你還是你
and I am still me.
我還是我
Dear friend.
摯友
Whether we're alive or dead.
無論是生還是死
Oh, right.
對了
I know I said not to think of revenge,
雖然我曾說過讓你不要再考慮復仇了
but I didn't mean you should renounce all hatred and become a saint either.
但我並不是要你放下憎恨 去成為聖人哦
Call it one of my little indulgences.
我這麼說 有一半是出於我的任性
P-Please…
求 求求你了
Stop…
不要啊
Easlies.
伊斯莉絲
The old lady and I were opposed to letting Corpse God see this…
雖說我和老太婆都反對 讓屍神殿看到這一幕…
I'm sorry!
對不起啊
Forgive me!
饒 饒了我吧
Taking on people's dirty work is my duty.
替子民處理骯髒的工作 是我的分內之事
So…
所以
There's no need for you to get your hands dirty,
你就沒必要弄髒自己的手了
my dear friend.
摯友
Such conceited thinking is
正因為您有這種自以為是的想法
what got you assassinated, Your Majesty.
所以你才會遭人暗殺 陛下
Maybe so.
或許吧
So he's disappeared.
他消失了嗎
I'd planned to wait and see what would happen,
我本來還打算暫時觀察一下情況的
but I guess I'll start tomorrow.
但我們還是明天就行動吧
This city's absolutely crawling with troublemakers.
看來這座城市裡有很多麻煩事呢
We've got the bug and my comrade from back home.
蟲子和同鄉
Which should I prioritize first?
我應該先從哪一邊開始呢
My wish remains the same as it was before, Your Majesty.
我的願望一直都沒有改變 陛下
I wish for a world where everyone can live in peace.
我渴求的是 一個大家都能和平生活的世界
A world where you don't have to get your hands dirty.
一個您不再需要把自己弄髒的世界
That's why
所以
I have to venture even deeper.
我需要進一步地深入
Into the shadows of that world which are blending into this one.
直到到達混在這個世界裡的 那個世界的陰暗處為止
Mr. Habaki.
幅木先生
I hope the higher-ups will
在你說出我的事情之前
take care of you before you reveal me.
我真希望你能被上面的人給處理掉
It seems that I need to hide for a while.
看來我需要暫時躲起來了
I'll have to lose this phone somewhere in the next few hours-
這個手機也得在幾個小時內 在某個地方處理…
Hot!
好燙
Oh dear. You dropped your phone.
哎呀 你的手機掉了哦
Sorry about that.
是啊 不好意思…
Huh?
咦
Huh? Wait.
那個 等一下
Excuse me?
抱歉…
Hands and feet.
手…腳
of Sabaramond.
塞巴拉隆多的…
-Eyes. -Ears.
-眼睛 -耳朵
Catch him.
抓住他…
Maybe I shouldn't have run away. This is bad.
要是之前我沒逃跑就好了 這下糟了
Oh, hello? Polka?
啊 喂 是波爾卡嗎
We are back.
我們已經回到大樓裡了
Is everything okay with you?
你那邊沒事吧
Yeah, I'm with Miss Clarissa now.
嗯 我現在跟克拉麗莎小姐 她們在一起
Will packing tape do?
用膠帶就可以了嗎
For nice.
現在就先這樣吧
This sure is well made.
這做得不錯嘛
Aren't you surprised?
妳不驚訝嗎
About what?
這有什麼好驚訝地
This is Shinoyama company tech, right?
這是四乃山家公司的技術吧
I've asked them to create a shark robot before.
我還拜託過公司 給我做一個鯊魚型機器人呢
I-I see…
啊 是嗎
Besides, I always knew you were keeping at least one or two secrets from me, Xiaoyu.
而且 我也知道小幽你身上 多少有一兩個秘密
I mean, if you could transform into a shark or something,
如果你說你其實能變身成鯊魚的話
then I'd definitely be surprised, and I'd probably ask you to marry me.
我說不定會大吃一驚並向你求婚
Get married…
求婚…
Even if you can't tell me your secrets, there are still some things I know.
就算你不願說出自己的秘密 有些事我也是明白的
I know you've worked so hard to protect us.
你是為了保護我們而努力的吧
Thank you.
謝謝你
No…
不對 不對
I only acted
我只是
for my own benefit.
為了自己而已
Kurupon, answer the phone.
匠匠 你來接電話
Hmm?
我嗎
Hello, Takumi?
喂 匠
I heard you hurt your leg.
我聽說你的腳受傷了
Drop by the bar later.
你等等來酒吧一趟吧
I'll ask Kazami to take a look at you and give you some medicine.
我會讓風見準備好藥品給你治療的
Look, all I need is to stop the bleeding…
啊 這點小傷只要止住血…
No arguing. Just get it treated.
別說了 讓我們給你治療一下
Geez.
唉
Injuries worry me.
要小心處理傷口
An injury that's not treated properly
如果處理不當
can come back to haunt you later.
可是會給以後的生活帶來影響的哦
Clarissa,
克拉麗莎
your vision…
妳的視力…
Polka, I need you to ask her something
波爾卡 我想請你幫我問麗莎一件事
Um…
那個…
Miss Clarissa, why do you care about this Habaki person?
克拉麗莎小姐 妳為什麼要在意那個姓幅木的男人
Well…
那個…
You're curious?
你想知道嗎
Yes.
也是呢
I was just too stubborn.
我只是太執著了
The reason I was able to find him
我之所以能找到他
was thanks to the information from the police.
還是多虧了來自警察內部的情報
It can't be. Just who?
什麼 到底是誰
ONE HOUR AGO So you can get Habaki's location.
(一小時前) 你知道幅木在哪對嗎
Yes. I planted a GPS chip in his sleeve.
是的 因為我在他袖子上 安裝了GPS晶片
You're sure you this is what you want? Mr. Tozawa?
你覺得這樣就可以了嗎 戶澤先生
Yes. I've thought it through.
是的 這是我的判斷
I know that my grandfather saved your wife once.
雖然我知道我的祖父救過你的夫人
Do you feel so indebted to me that you would betray Tsubaki Iwanome?
但這份恩情 值得讓你去背叛岩野目椿嗎
It's not about repaying any debt.
這不是恩情的問題
I don't think this incident falls into the category of even a troublemaker.
這次的事件 恐怕不僅僅是災厄的程度了
I want Iwanome to be an upstanding police inspector.
我希望岩野目係長是個正直的警察
I don't want him to stray from that path the way I did.
希望他不要像我一樣走了歪路
You're awfully overprotective of him.
你對他真是關照有加啊
He's competent,
他雖然很能幹
but he's still fragile.
但他還很脆弱
Until he's… No…
在他…不
Until Comps-3 has matured, I want them to walk the straight and narrow.
在三輯成熟之前 我希望他能走一條正路
That's all this is about.
只是出於這個原因而已
Okay! Let's start by taking a fresh look at Inspector Habaki's call log.
好 首先我們要重新調查一下 幅木警視正的通話紀錄
Not only that. Check all precinct and town surveillance cameras.
還要調查警察廳內和街上的監控
See who's had any contact with Habaki and the police officer who killed himself.
要查出和幅木還有自殺的警察 接觸過的所有人
Yes, sir!
是
DO NOT DWELL ON THE PAST. THE FILTH HAS ALREADY PERMEATED THE UPPER LEVELS I'll be in charge this with Arase.
(不要執著於過去…汙穢已經滲入上層…) 我和荒瀨負責這邊
You sure are pulling out all the stops.
你挺有幹勁的嘛
I know it's not fair to you, but I might still be a little emotional, you know?
不好意思 或許我現在還很感情用事
No matter how hard I try, I will never catch Hosorogi.
我知道就算我去找細呂木先生 也還是找不到他
So we'll just need him to come to us.
既然這樣 那就只能讓他來找我們了
Have him come to us?
讓他過來嗎
How?
要怎麼做
We'll use force.
這就需要體力勞動了
We're going to completely smoke out the organization that Habaki is a part of.
我要徹底調查幅木所屬的那個組織
It's likely "Sabaramond" is the key word here.
那個塞巴拉隆多恐怕就是關鍵字
We're going to arrest everyone who is related.
把跟他們有關的傢伙都揪出來
I'm just making a place that Mr. Hosorogi will come home to.
我只不過是想創造出 能讓細呂木先生回來的條件而已
Let's say, uh…
那個 如果
If I could find Mr. Hosorogi's soul,
我找到了細呂木先生的靈魂
is there anything you'd want to tell him?
妳有什麼話要告訴他嗎
Huh?
嗯
Polka?
波爾卡
I'm sorry for doing this without your permission.
抱歉是我自作主張了
Yes.
是啊
I trampled all over his wishes.
我踐踏了那個人的願望
Mr. Miyabi wouldn't like to see what I've turned into.
雅先生一定不喜歡現在的我
He doesn't like it.
他並不喜歡
According to my grandfather, I inherited the intermediary agency.
按照祖父的想法繼承了仲介屋 這個不為人知的家業的我
But I am who I am.
但是我已經成為了現在的我
That's an undeniable truth, and I have no regrets over it.
這是不可否認的事實 因此我不後悔
So,
所以
there's just one thing I'd want to say.
我只有一句話想對他說
If that person comes back,
如果那個人回來了
there's one thing I should say to him first.
我只會先對他說這句話…
Mr. Hosorogi.
細呂木先生
Farewell.
再見了
My beloved.
我曾經愛過的人
I look forward to continuing to work with you.
以後也請多多指教了
Huh?
那個
What's going on here?
這到底是…
Hm.
嗯
I see you're awake.
看來你醒了啊
Who is this?
他是誰
Misaki! Takumi!
美咲 匠
Welcome back.
辛苦了
Misaki, it seems you're okay.
美咲 看來妳沒事啊
Yes, I'm fine.
嗯 我活蹦亂跳的呢
Takumi.
匠
If you like, I could use a flesh-restoring spell.
如果可以的話 讓我對你 使用修復肉體的魔法吧
Huh? You can do that?
什麼 這也可以嗎
I'd have to make part of your body a zombie first.
只要我暫時讓你一部分的身體 變成屍體的話…
No, thanks, I'll stick with the regular treatment.
算了 普通的治療就可以了
If I'm ever mortally wounded, though, you can bet I'll be asking you then.
不過 等我受到了致命傷的 到時再拜託你吧
Hm.
嗯
Things can't carry on like this.
這樣下去不行
If I want a world where I can live in peace with everyone,
既然我希望大家都能過上平穩的生活
I need to be willing to take more determined steps toward that end.
那我就需要進一步地深入才行
I have to go much deeper as the "Corpse God"
作為屍神殿
into this world.
深入這個世界
Hmm. A moment of your time.
嗯 我問一下
Who is this we have sitting here?
坐在這裡的人是誰
An innocent, average citizen who happened to learn Fire-breathing Bug's true identity?
他並不是知道了 你們赴火之蟲真面目的普通人吧
Perhaps
他恐怕是
you're with Habaki from the precinct?
幅木的同夥
In other words, he's a party concerned with this symbol.
也就是說 他是跟這個符號有關的人吧
So far you've burned every last person related to the organization.
至今為止你們一個不剩地 燒死了很多與組織有關的人
But you must have realized your way of doing things had drawbacks.
但是也許你們已經認識到 這種做法是有極限的了
When the organization goes public,
組織被世人所知
the situation will change drastically.
今後的情況也會發生巨大的變化
So you tried a new approach!
於是你們嘗試了新的辦法
The root of the organization is key.
為了摧毀組織的根源 應該先找到其根源之所在
In other words,
也就是說
having dragged this man and Habaki to the forefront, you mean to rely on my abilities?
因為我把他和幅木都引了出來 所以你們想借助我的力量嗎
That's exactly it.
正是…如此
That's right.
你說得…對
As I'd expect from you.
不愧…是你
Sometimes, being a magician requires the art of conversation.
對於一個魔術師來說 有時話術是很重要的
This much is only natural for me.
這種程度不過是小菜一碟 為此我…
I thought he was just a criminal with a screw loose, but…
我還以為他只是一個 腦袋壞掉的犯罪分子
-The magician's operation… -This was actually all thoroughly calculated.
-魔術師手術中… -看來一切都在他精密的計算之中
-So that's what it is. -Right?
-原來是這麼一回事啊 -是吧
I've actually hit the nail on the head.
沒想到我竟然說對了
Though I'd hoped to react with surprise after being told, "You're totally wrong"!
我本以為你們會說我錯了 然後讓我大吃一驚的
Um…
那個
I have no idea what any of this has to do with me,
我不知道你在說什麼
so could you just let me go home?
能請你們放我走嗎
Mm.
嗯
I can tell that you're involved with all the troublemakers.
既然你跟各種災厄有關 那我就能隱約感覺到一些事情
You've got the smell of someone who's killed countless people.
我感覺到你身上 有種殺過很多人的味道
So anything I do will be forgiven.
既然如此 那無論你做什麼都能被原諒
Or I'm screwed!
or die（或是死）
Do you have any proof?
你有什麼科學的依據嗎
If I'm just an ordinary citizen,
如果我只是個普通人
won't this whole mix-up be a terrible blow to your pride?
你的自尊就會受到傷害嗎
Worry not.
放心吧
My pride is still
我的自尊現在還在
PRIDE in a jail cell.
(自尊) 拘留所裡
Mm? What?
啥 什麼
The fact is, I am a bother to ordinary citizens.
再說了 事到如今我怎麼可能還怕 會給一般人添麻煩呢
Especially when I abducted PM Kubikigawara.
特別是在綁架了頸城瓦總理的時候
As a result of my actions, a lot of companies' stock prices took a dive.
畢竟我讓很多公司的股價都下跌了
It seems Solitaire infiltrated the police station.
警視廳似乎遭到了雪天鴉的入侵
Damn joyful offender.
可惡的愉快犯
Looks like there was movement in Polka's building too.
波爾卡所在的大樓好像也有動作吧
Yes.
嗯
The intelligence dealer was wounded.
情報販子受傷了
And the young lady's bodyguard
至於大小姐的護衛
had one of his prosthetic limbs cut off.
他的一隻義手被砍斷了
It's possible they had a run-in with an enemy force of some kind.
他們恐怕是跟某個敵對勢力交戰過吧
So formal.
真是見外啊
He's still a part of your family, remember?
那個護衛也是你們雷家的人吧
He cut ties with the Lei family.
不 我們雷家 已經跟那傢伙斷絕關係了
No need to worry.
您無需擔心
Even so, he is still rather capable.
不過他也有一定的實力
Our opponent isn't just some small-time punk, is what you're saying.
也就是說 對方並不是那種 隨處可見的小嘍囉嗎
The enemy's hand has gradually reached us.
我認為敵人的手 已經慢慢伸到我們這邊來了
Oh?
是嗎
Since nightfall, a number of the lookouts have been attacked.
從昨晚開始 就有幾名負責監視的人被殺掉了
Everyone's phone has been invaded.
所有人的手機都遭到了入侵
In other words, someone is looking for information.
也就是說 敵人在打探我們的情報嗎
What's more…
還有更奇怪的事
All the money in my bank account has disappeared.
我帳戶裡的存款全都不見了
So they're attacking individuals as well?
他們還展開了針對個人的攻擊嗎
Look into it, Bao.
妳去調查一下 暴
Roger.
收到
ACCOUNT BALANCE 237,380,000 JAPANESE YEN That really is a huge sum of money deposited.
(帳戶餘額 237,380,000日圓) 真的匯進來了一大筆錢
I TRANSFERRED ALL TAIPEI'S MONEY TO YOUR ACCOUNT My sister is so merciless.
(我把太貝帳戶裡的錢全都轉到你的帳戶裡了…) 姐姐她真是毫不留情啊
Oh right,
對了
I need to report the matter of the arm to Master.
我得向主公大人報告手臂的事才行
Hey. It's me.
喂 是我
I heard.
我聽說了
One of your arms got ruined.
你的一隻手臂好像壞了 對吧
Huh? Yeah…
呃 是…是的
I had a run-in with the Agakura.
我剛阿牙倉打了一場
Ah, yeah, I heard about that too.
啊 這件事我也聽說了
Huh?
咦
What matters is that you're alive.
你能保住性命就是萬幸了
And I hear you protected the guys from the building too.
你還保護了大樓裡的那個傢伙吧
You did well.
你做得很好
Thank you, Xiaoyu.
謝謝你了 小幽
Y-You don't have to thank me, Master!
您 您不用謝我啦 主公大人
So how are your arms and legs?
那你剩下的手和腳怎麼樣了
All good.
都沒事
My arm's completely destroyed,
這一隻手完全壞了
so it looks like I'll have to get by one-handed for a while.
看來我暫時只能靠另一隻手生活了
I'm so sorry.
非常抱歉
I broke the thing you gave me, Master.
我弄壞了您給我的東西
Don't worry about it.
你不必在意
And…
另外
The guy behind you says he'll take care of it for you.
你後面的傢伙說 他會想辦法處理你的手臂
Behind me?
後面
When did he get here?
你什麼時候來的
Xiaoyu. I heard about
小幽 我聽說了
you saving Takumi.
是你救了匠吧
I only acted because not doing so may have allowed harm to come to Lady Sayo.
因為對方想要傷害小夜大小姐 所以我才這麼做的
Please let me prepare you a new arm.
可以讓我為你準備手臂嗎
My job is to protect the Shinoyamas.
我的工作是守護四乃山家
That's why…
正因如此
I don't trust you.
我才不能相信你
The person who was under the floor in Mr. Rozan's room…
之前躲在呂算先生房間地板下的人
Was it you, wasn't it?
就是你吧
I could tell right away because of your unique color of the soul.
因為你靈魂的顏色很特別 所以我馬上就知道了
That's also how I knew you already recognized me as a fake.
所以 我也已經知道 你知道我是冒牌貨了
Color of the soul?
靈魂的顏色
What are you talking about?
你到底在說什麼啊
I'll explain everything.
我會一一向你解釋的
So, first of all,
所以首先
I want you to have a serious bout with me.
我希望你能認真地跟我打一場
What?
什麼
This is just what I wanted.
正好
I'm going to expose who he really is to the Master.
我要在主公大人的面前撕下他的偽裝
Don't think I'll bow my head to you in front of the Master.
你別以為我只會對主公大人點頭哈腰
I'm not thinking that at all.
我沒有…
You saved Takumi. There's no need for you to defer to me.
你救了匠 所以你沒必要低頭
Enough talk. Take your stance.
別廢話了 放馬過來吧
Oh, it's not me who's going to fight with you.
並不是我要跟你交手
It is my power, so it's almost the same thing.
不過你要交手的是我的力量 說是跟我交手也沒錯吧
Your opponent will be this dual-fanged tiger.
你的對手是雙牙虎
Though it can't maintain for long,
雖然我沒辦法召喚牠太久
show me your strength as best you can.
但我希望你能盡可能展現你的實力
What is this monster?
這是什麼怪物啊
A hallucination? Hypnosis?
是幻覺嗎 還是催眠
Oh dear.
哎呀
The situation is even more exaggerated than I expected.
事情真是比我想像中還要誇張啊
When I received your call last night, I was really taken aback.
我昨晚接到你的電話時真是嚇了一跳
The Agakura are the ones who picked off his limbs.
說起阿牙倉 就是他們卸下了小幽的四肢
I thought he'd do something reckless and put his life in danger.
我還擔心他會不會不顧安危地亂來呢
It's easy to tell him,
“不要勉強”
"Don't push yourself too hard. If you want to run away, you can run away."
“想逃跑的時候就跑” 這些話說起來很簡單
But that makes him all the more determined to do the opposite.
可是說出來後那傢伙反倒會亂來
I can see that.
我能理解
I've seen plenty of people who prioritize their feelings over their lives.
至今為止我也見到過很多 將內心的想法看得比性命還重的人
By the way,
話說回來
if your goal is to live in peace,
要是讓小幽也知道了你的祕密
then I'd have figured you'd want to keep your secret from Xiaoyu.
說不定平穩的生活 會進一步離你遠去哦
Yeah.
是啊
In holding back,
但是 如果我心有顧慮
one can end up losing so much more.
那就只會讓我失去更多東西
For the sake of my future peace,
為了未來
let's put it aside for now.
我還是先讓它暫時遠去吧
Let's stop here.
到此為止吧
I've got the picture.
我大致清楚了
Thank you, Gufa. Rafa.
謝謝你們 古法和勞法
Ah! Hey!
啊 喂
Sorry, they seem to really like you.
抱歉 牠們好像很喜歡你
Um…
那個
Anyway, take a shower first.
我覺得你還是先去洗個澡會比較好
If only my right arm and legs were in full working order…
如果我的右手和腳沒有問題的話…
No, I took that bout as seriously as any I've fought.
不 這的確是一場 讓我使出了全力的較量
But he…
可是那傢伙
Even with that incomprehensible power…
他那無法理解的力量
I'm certain he was far from taking our bout seriously.
恐怕還遠遠不是他的全力吧
Oh.
啊
Welcome back.
你來了
This is what the joints look like.
我身上的接口是這樣的
So can you do something about my arm?
所以…你有什麼辦法 能處理我的手臂嗎
Thank you.
謝謝你
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字
You must have a real name.
你應該有真正的名字吧
Your strength is indisputable.
你的實力是貨真價實的
So it doesn't feel right for me
(機械人 鯊魚雀躍) 我也不能允許我自己
HAPPY SHARK DANCE to keep referring to you as "the fake."
繼續叫你冒牌貨
Most people call me,
通用名可以嗎
"Corpse God."
我叫屍神殿
That's quite the hefty title.
你這個通用名也太誇張了吧
Yes, I think so too.
是啊 我自己也這麼覺得
Speaking of which, didn't you challenge me to
話說
that fight to make the pecking order clear once and for all?
這場較量本身 就是為了調整我的新手臂吧
I risked my life and pride.
我可是拚上了性命和自尊
So, what are you planning to do about my arm?
然後呢 你打算怎麼處理我的手臂
Oh, I just finished.
啊 嗯 已經完成了
Huh?
什麼 什麼
Whose arm is this?
這是什麼手啊
Answer me! Corpse God!
回答我 屍神殿
Urdwigia.
烏爾德維西亞
It's the right arm of the colossal lighting dragon that used to bathe the world in electricity.
這是曾經讓世界電閃雷鳴的 傀雷龍的右手
Dragon?
龍…
Xiaoyu.
小幽
I want to make a deal in exchange for this arm.
我想用這隻手臂跟你做個交易
As the fourth-ranking sorcerer in the imperial court,
我希望你能與身為 帝國宮廷魔法師第四位的我
I want you to make an alliance with me.
結為同盟
(Episode 20: The Visitors)
(#20 The Visitors-來訪者-)